http://www.mountosb.org/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Who we are
Our website address is mountosb.org. We are a religious community located in Atchison, Kansas. Our mission is to serve God through community life, prayer, ministry, and care for all creation.
What personal data we collect and why we collect it
Comments
When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.
An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.
Media
If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.
Contact forms
We use the contact information given in our contact forms specifically for the purpose of that specified form. Mount St. Scholastica does not share information given in our contact forms with any external companies or organizations unless given permission by the submitter.
We use the standard Elementor forms for most places on our website. However, Sophia Spirituality Center, Retreats, Spiritual Direction, Program Offerings, Private Retreats & Hermitage, and Groups & Space rental all use google forms. In any form, the user has the option to not allow their data to be collected
Cookies
If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.
If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.
When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.
If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.
Embedded content from other websites
Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.
These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.
Analytics
Who we share your data with
Mount St. Scholastica uses MonsterInsights google analytics to track hits on our site. However, we anonymize IP addresses and any personal information. We do not use this information for advertising, nor do we sell your information to external companies. Any personal information is freely given in an online form and used solely for the purpose of that form.
How long we retain your data
If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.
For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.
What rights you have over your data
If you have an account on this site or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.
Where we send your data
Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.
Your contact information
For more information contact:
Diana Seago: diana@mountosb.org
Additional information
How we protect your data
We have a firewall and website protection system in place to ensure your data will not be taken in an unauthorized manner. We do not give or sell your information to external organizations or companies. All our forms have google captcha extensions to protect against viruses and spam-keeping your information safe!
What data breach procedures we have in place
If a data breach should occur, we will contact those directly affected via email and phone.
What third parties we receive data from
We use MonsterInsights with the EU Compliance addon for google analytics. This allows us to anonymize user data, such as IP addresses, with tracking on our website.
What automated decision making and/or profiling we do with user data
We use automated decision making to send requested newsletters and additional information about Mount St. Scholastica, Keeler Women’s Center, and Sophia Center to subjects who fill out the corresponding forms online.
Industry regulatory disclosure requirements
By submitting a form on www.mountosb.org, you give Mount St. Scholastica permission to send any requested information to the corresponding person, street address, email, phone number, etc.
Search for:
Recent PostsHomily for the Immaculate ConceptionDecember 8, 2020Homily for the Second Sunday of AdventDecember 6, 2020Thanksgiving Day ReflectionDecember 2, 2020Reflection for the First Sunday in AdventNovember 30, 2020COVID-19: Nov. 20 UpdateJuly 28, 2020
Top
Neve | Powered by Wordpress
Mount St. Scholastica 2020
